https://www.american-rails.com/privacy-policy.html

American-Rails.com
Menu
HomeA-R.com Blog
Rail HistoryIndustry HistoryFallen FlagsTycoons And BaronsFamous LandmarksStreamliners
LocomotivesLocomotive HistorySteam LocomotivesDiesel LocomotivesElectric Locomotives
Rolling StockPassenger Car TypesFreight Car Types
Today's IndustryClass IsRegionalsShort LinesRail MaintenanceRail Infrastructure
OdditiesInterurbansNarrow Gauge RailroadsLogging LinesRailroad Stories
Rail TravelAmtrakTravel By TrainRail ToursCommuter RailTourist Train Rides
MoreMuseumsStations And DepotsRailroad JobsState HistoryGlossary And Terms
MiscellaneousMagazinesThe NewsletterPrivacy PolicyTerms Of UseBook Reviews
The American-Rails.com Privacy Policy
At American-Rails.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use American-Rails.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.American-Rails.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.About Our CookiesA cookie is a string of information that American-Rails.com stores on your computer, which your browser provides to American-Rails.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.American-Rails.com  uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which will store and use this information on its servers. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://policies.google.com/privacy.Google Analytics CookiesAmerican-Rails.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your usage of it.If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out browser extension or add-on at: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/Advertising CookiesWe use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website.You may opt out of personalized ads for over 135 different ad networks. Click here to do that.  In addition, if you would like to opt out of interest-based advertising provided by Network Advertising Initiative members, or manage such ads on your browser please click here to do that.Some third-party advertisements are served by Google. Google's cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of personalized ads by visiting the Google ad opt-out page.This link from Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad products.Refusing CookiesYou can set your browser to accept or refuse all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse American-Rails.com's cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.Personally Identifiable InformationAmerican-Rails.com may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:To run and operate our site.To display content on the site correctly.To improve customer service.To help us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize your user experience.To understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our site.To improve our site.To improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature.To send information to you that you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.To send periodic emails, which may include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.To respond to your enquiries, questions, and/or other requests.American-Rails.com may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.  To learn more about personally identifiable information please click here.If you complete a form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for information relevant to the purpose of the form.You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor's IP address, which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other purpose.Non-personally Identifiable InformationWe may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar information.Children's Privacy ProtectionThis website is directed to adults. It is not directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.California Consumer Privacy ActThe California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) became effective on January 1, 2020 and is a new type of privacy law which establishes various rights to California state residents.  It specifically targets companies which do business in California and earn revenue, carry out data processing, and potentially sell California residents' personal information.  As such, the companies which do this must provide residents the right to opt out of the "sale" of their "personal information" as the law defines and provide this opt-out via a prominent "Do Not Sell My Personal Information" link on the "selling" party’s homepage.  Please note, American-Rails.com has not sold any personal information about consumers in 2020.  In addition, American-Rails.com has never sold any such information since the site was founded in 2007. Release of InformationIf we sell American-Rails.com, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our host's servers. That host is SiteSell Inc., located at 1000 Saint-Jean Boulevard, Suite 702, Pointe-Claire, QC H9R 5P1 Canada.If you wish to review your information stored on the SiteSell servers for American-Rails.com, click on this link. You can also edit, download or delete any of your information from the servers by clicking on that link.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website and would like to update that information or have it deleted from our records, click on this link.Updates and Effective DateAmerican-Rails.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to American-Rails.com's privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of this privacy policy in its entirety.  Finally, if you would like to review your personal information please click here.Last updated:  October 8, 2020
This Form cannot be submitted until the missing fields (labelled below in red) have been filled in
American-Rails.com Privacy Policy Consent
Please note that all fields followed by an asterisk must be filled in.
First Name*
Last Name*
E-Mail Address*
Web Site URL
Street Address
City
State/Prov
Zip/Postal Code
Country*CountryUnited StatesCanada----------------AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntiguaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGrenadaGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribadiNorth KoreaSouth KoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoFederated States of MicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMontenegroMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaS. Georgia and S. Sandwich Isls.Saint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. HelenaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSudanSurinameSvalbardSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamUS Virgin IslandsWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslavia (former)ZaireZambiaZimbabwe
Home Phone
Business Phone
Fax
GDPR*
I am at least 16 years of age.
I have read and accept the privacy policy.
I understand that you will use my information to contact me or send me the information I requested.
Please enter the word that you see below.
Home
›
Privacy Policy
HomeA-R.com BlogRail HistoryIndustry HistoryFallen FlagsTycoons And BaronsFamous LandmarksStreamlinersLocomotivesLocomotive HistorySteam LocomotivesDiesel LocomotivesElectric LocomotivesRolling StockPassenger Car TypesFreight Car TypesToday's IndustryClass IsRegionalsShort LinesRail MaintenanceRail InfrastructureOdditiesInterurbansNarrow Gauge RailroadsLogging LinesRailroad StoriesRail TravelAmtrakTravel By TrainRail ToursCommuter RailTourist Train RidesMoreMuseumsStations And DepotsRailroad JobsState HistoryGlossary And TermsMiscellaneousMagazinesThe NewsletterPrivacy PolicyTerms Of UseBook Reviews
© Copyright 2007-2020 American-Rails.com. All content copyright American-Rails.com (unless otherwise noted). All photos and videos, copyright individual owners/organizations.
